<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Liepaja Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="category_classics">Classics</string>
    <string name="category_active_leisure">Active Leisure</string>
    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_dining">Dining</string>

    <!-- Active Leisure -->
    <string name="tarzan">Tarzan\'s Obstacle Park</string>
    <string name="tarzan_description">Tarzan\'s Obstacle Park consists of 5 tracks and 76 different
        obstacles placed in trees up to 15 meters above the ground. It will be interesting for both
        children and adults, since the tracks are tailored to different interests.</string>
    <string name="karosta_prison">Karosta Prison</string>
    <string name="karosta_prison_description">Offers guided tours in Karosta Prison and museum, show
        "Behind Bars", accommodation and Extreme Night in prison. Different activities in Northern
         Forts like guided tour, Spy game Escape from USSR and Labyrinth of Senses.</string>
    <string name="children_playground">Children Playground</string>
    <string name="children_playground_description">Every Sunday from June 1st till September 1st at
        midday 12:00 leisure activities, puppet theatre or cirkus performances for children.</string>
    <string name="archery_range">"Archery Liepaja" 3D archery range</string>
    <string name="arechery_range_description">There are up to 20 different 3D animal targets in the
        3D archery range, which are placed so that anyone would be able to shoot.</string>
    <string name="windsurfing_club">Windsurfing Club "Rietumkrasts"</string>
    <string name="windsurfing_club_description">Recreation on the water - windsurfing, kite-surfing,
        water-skiing, bladders, water-motorbikes, motorboats. Rentals and lessons. Portable kitchen,
        sauna, tent places.</string>
    <string name="bb_wakepark">Active Leisure Park "BB wakepark"</string>
    <string name="bb_wakepark_description">In summer, "BB wakepark" has the variety of offers as
        wakeboarding track and equipment rentals, SUP board and boats rental, and for the full
        relaxation, sauna and hot-tub services.</string>
    <string name="boat_rental">Boat rental "Niknās laivas"</string>
    <string name="boat_rental_description">Furious and comfortable boat rental for trips in Liepāja
        Trade Canal and Lake, as well as in rivers of Kurzeme.</string>
    <string name="quest_house">Quest House</string>
    <string name="quest_house_description">Quest House – is a unique adventure – offers you an
        interesting team game for groups of 2-4 people. You get locked in a room, in  order to
        escape you should examine all hides, using hints and clues solve all riddles, applying your
        logics and savvy.</string>
    <string name="ship_and_catamaran_rent">Ship Četri vēji and catamaran rent</string>
    <string name="ship_and_catamaran_rent_description">Boat trips in Liepāja port area and the sea.
        Boarding at the yacht port in Liepāja promenade. Fishing in the sea and long boat trips.</string>

    <!-- Nature -->
    <string name="liepaja_lake">Liepaja Lake</string>
    <string name="liepaja_lake_description">A lagoon-type lake that was formed with the retreat of
        the Baltic Sea. An important waterfowl nesting and transit place during migration periods.
        During the nesting period many bird species that are threatened in Europe find their shelter
        here. The lake and its surrounding meadows are a nature reserve area. There are two bird
        watching towers one the lake.</string>
    <string name="liepaja_beach">Liepaja Beach</string>
    <string name="liepaja_beach_description">The beach is 50 to 80 m wide when the wind is calm, and
        it has white fine sand which amazes even those who have been to the world\'s most famous
        beach resorts. After a strong wind you can find some pieces of amber washed ashore. \n
        Liepāja has a first beach in Latvia, adjusted for people with special needs.</string>
    <string name="seaside_park">Seaside Park</string>
    <string name="seaside_park_description">Liepaja is very proud of the park. It was developed at
        the end of the 19th century. The park is 3 km long with a total area of 70 ha and is one of
        the largest planted parks in Latvia. It is the home of Latvias largest drums, nouveau
        fountain, The Swan Pond, Monument for sailors and fishermen lost at sea, children
        playground and much more.</string>
    <string name="raina_park">Raina Park</string>
    <string name="raina_park_description">This is a landscape park, developed at the 19th century.
        Also has a children playground</string>
    <string name="southern_breakwater">Sauthern Breakwater</string>
    <string name="southern_breakwater_description">When having a walk on the beach, supplement it
    with a sightseeing on the Sauthern Breakwater for even nicer memories.</string>
    <string name="northern_breakwater">Northern Breakwater</string>
    <string name="northern_breakwater_description">1800 meters long, this breakwater is a famous
        place for the locals to enjoy the beaty of nature during storms.</string>
    <string name="seaside_park_velo_track">Seaside Velo-track</string>
    <string name="seaside_park_velo_track_description">The Seaside Velo-track is a beautiful place
        in Liepaja for bike rides and strolls. You\'ll wish you could take the pine and sea smell
        with you!</string>

    <!-- Classics -->
    <string name="great_amber">Concert Hall Great Amber</string>
    <string name="great_amber_description">The new concert hall Great Amber is a regional centre of
        culture and events, home to the Liepaja Symphony Orchestra, Liepaja Music, Art and Design
        High School, as well as the concert hall’s manager and event producer - LLC Great Amber.
    Its acoustics have been created by world leaders in their fields – Prof. Karlheinz Müller of
        Müller BBM, Germany, and Prof. Christian Bartenbach of Bartenbach, Germany, respectively.</string>
    <string name="musicians_alley">The Latvian Musicians Alley</string>
    <string name="musicians_alley_description">The Latvian Musicians Alley of Fame was opened in
        2006, with its 40 bronze plaques each with handprints of musicians, 12 plaques honoring
        current and former music bands, and 5 plaques dedicated to musicians who are not with us
        any more.</string>
    <string name="rose_square">Rose Square</string>
    <string name="rose_square_description">The heart of Liepāja is its Rose Square, located in the heart of the city
        centre. In 1910, city authorities decided to construct a public rosegarden. Hence, in 1911
        the square was given the name Rose Square, its name to this day. The coats of arms of
        Liepāja\'s sister cities are placed on the edging around the bed of roses.</string>
    <string name="anthem_characters">Sculptures of Liepāja Anthem Characters</string>
    <string name="anthem_characters_description">The song is frozen in bronze and yet it can be
        heard. Everyone walking towards the sea along Kūrmājas prospekts will be followed by a gaze
        of curious crow, a boatman known also as a coffin-maker, a telephone technician climbed on a
        pole, and a crouching forest of people… “Pilsētā, kurā piedzimst vējš…” (City where the wind
        is born) is a song of particular importance for the residents of Liepāja.</string>
    <string name="applied_arts_center">Applied Arts Centre</string>
    <string name="applied_arts_center_description">In Applied Arts Centre you can meet the masters of Applied Arts Studio "Kursa",
        "Liepava" and "Zītars" which manage our immaterial cultural heritage. Weavers, knitters and
        amber jewelery makers demonstrate their skills and organize workshops to teach applied arts
        skills.</string>
    <string name="house_of_craftsmen">The House of Craftsmen</string>
    <string name="house_of_craftsmen_description">The House of Craftsmen offers to view and try out the wide variety of Latvian
        traditional crafts – amber processing, weaving, minting of coins, making jewellery and
        pottery, as well as to watch the making of modern pieces of art such as silk painting,
        tapestry, felting, etc.
        The exhibition of the House of Craftsmen displays the national costumes of Lejaskurzeme counties,
        some of which are more than a century old, Latvian longest amber string of beads, artworks
        of local craftsmen and ancient tools used by our ancestors – craftsmen.</string>
    <string name="peter_market">The Peter Market</string>
    <string name="peter_market_description">The Peter Market is located on Kurshu square
        (Kuršu laukums) and still is the largest market in the city. The pavilion of the market was
        opened in 1910. It was designed by the architect Melvil. The pavilion had an innovative
        shape for those times.</string>
    <string name="occupation_museum">Museum Liepāja during the Occupation Regimes</string>
    <string name="occupation_museum_description">Permanent display tells about social, political,
        economic and cultural life in Liepāja and its region during German and Soviet occupation in
        1939-1991 and how the freedom of Latvia was regained in 1991. The house also hosts Jānis
        Lādītis’s photo collection exposition. Themed exhibitions of the museum’s collection and art
        displays are also organized here.</string>
    <string name="liepaja_museum">Liepaja Museum</string>
    <string name="liepaja_museum_description">The Liepāja Museum resides in one of the most beautiful 20th
        century buildings in Liepāja. The museum exhibition tells the history of the Liepāja City
        and its surrounding area from the Stone Age to the early 20th century. The museum also has
        on display an exposition dedicated to a wood carver Miķelis Pankoks (1894-1983) and two
        exhibition halls.</string>


    <!-- Dining -->
    <string name="reastaurant_piano">Piano</string>
    <string name="reastaurant_piano_description">The award-winning hotel restaurant Piano offers
        gourmet cuisine using organic products and its specialties: home-made fresh bread and ice
        cream. For an instant cultural experience you may enjoy exhibitions in the hotel art gallery
        Promenade, or watch the bright white sails go by during summer yacht regattas hosted by
        Liepaja Yacht Center right in front of the hotel.</string>
    <string name="house_of_food">House of Food</string>
    <string name="house_of_food_description">House Of Food is a place to eat good, quick international
        food from all corners of the world (please view the full menu below). Louie Fontaine, the
        owner and rock musician, has designed the place with a feel similar to a 50’s American
        diner, with an open kitchen and restaurant booths so high you’ll sit cosy and private in your
        own restaurant.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_libava">Libava</string>
    <string name="restaurant_libava_description">The restaurant Libava is located in an exclusive place
        on the bank of the Liepāja Trade Canal  in Recreational Centre “Libava” building. The restaurant
        Libava offers excellent cuisine with a vast selection of fish dishes and exquisite meat
        dishes, business lunch every weekday,  menu selected according to your needs for events
        organised at the recreational centre.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_oskars">Oskars</string>
    <string name="restaurant_oskars_description">One of the best restaurants in the city, located in
        Europa City Amrita Hotel</string>
    <string name="restaurant_upe">Upe</string>
    <string name="restaurant_upe_description">The restaurant is known for it\'s international cuisine
        and friendly service. Every customer that comes through the restaurant door is either a
        friend or will become one. Either its a quick lunch in the middle of your day, or a leisure
        evening with your friends while drinking wine - "Upe" will always guarantee the appropriate
        atmosphere and service.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_pastnieka_maja">Pastnieka Māja</string>
    <string name="restaurant_pastnieka_maja_description">This restaurant - separated from passing
        trams, cars and the hustle of pedestrians by a transparent glass wall - is located in the
        heart of Liepāja. The glass creates the feeling that the days hustle and reality is somehow
        remote and unreal, allowing guests to enjoy their break while sitting in the summer garden
        or calmly peering out through the windows.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_olive">Olive</string>
    <string name="restaurant_olive_description">Restaurant "Olive" offers a various choice of menu
        from cold snack and salads, meat and fish courses, pastas, pizzas, and also a variety of
        sushi. Kids menu is available as well. Open type kitchen gives you theclose insight into
        the process of cooking and the professional work of our chefs’ team.</string>


    <!-- Hotels -->
    <string name="promenade_hotel">Promenade Hotel</string>
    <string name="promenade_hotel_description">This old port warehouse stores the memories of a 200
        years long history and you may find a glimpse of it in every of the 50 guest rooms. The
        individual design of each room will preserve the magic of discovering something new every
        time you visit Promenade Hotel! Enjoy a sauna in the room, soft bathrobe and slippers or
        celebrate special moments at the marvelous banquet rooms!</string>
    <string name="fontaine_royal">Fontaine Royal</string>
    <string name="fontaine_royal_description">The hotel design is out of this world, full of royal furniture, all
        gold plated standing in contrast with the old factory spirit, you will feel like a king
        staying at the Fontaine Royal. The hotel has a music club in an old warehouse,
        (Fontaine Palace, capacity 600 people), offering live bands from around the globe.</string>
    <string name="hotel_libava">Libava</string>
    <string name="hotel_libava_description">The recreational centre Libava offers its guests seven hotel rooms
        equipped with modern amenities. Each room has a different design and interior. Guests also
        have the opportunity to enjoy a leisurely breakfast and romantic candlelight dinner in the
        winter garden with palm-trees and a fountain.</string>
    <string name="hotel_amrita">Europa City Amrita</string>
    <string name="hotel_amrita_description">You\'ll find here 83 comfortable rooms designed in a cosy
        Scandinavian style. Hotel offers a choice of room types  from single accommodation to luxury
        two room suites with steam saunas. Presidential suites located on two floors will surprise
        you with panoramic view over the town. 8 rooms are specially equipped for wheel chair users.</string>
    <string name="hotel_liva">Līva</string>
    <string name="hotel_liva_description">The hotel offers 115 guest rooms of different categories,
        a restaurant, bar and conference hall, as well as a parking lot under security surveillance.
        To preserve the competitiveness and meet best standards of hospitality renovation works are
        carried out on regular basis.</string>
    <string name="hotel_roze">Roze</string>
    <string name="hotel_roze_description">The guesthouse Roze is a little star on the shore of the
        Baltic Sea. The atmosphere of Jugendstil has been created in the
        antique detached house. Furniture, pictures, restaurant-bar, tea room and winter garden -
        everything holds the atmosphere of the time and style of the beginning of the 20th century.</string>
    <string name="hotel_fontaine">Fontaine Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_fontaine_description">The Hotel is located on a small cobblestone street,
        towards the canal, 500 m from the beach, with a nice backyard.  Hotel can accommodate 44
        people in 18 different rooms. Each room has its own design and charm, a true adventure.
        Guests can oder breakfast.</string>
    <string name="hotel_vilhelmine">Vilhelmīne</string>
    <string name="hotel_vilhelmine_description">There are 3 floors with 10 rooms. All rooms are
        large, bright and cosy with obsolete, old, and at the same time, modern atmosphere. Mansard
        floor has 2 minilux rooms with nice view to the old city. There are preserved old wooden
        beams and other antique elements on the mansard floor.</string>
    <string name="hotel_ezera_maja">Ezera Māja</string>
    <string name="hotel_ezera_maja_description">Ezera Maja is situated on the street that connects
        the Baltic sea and Liepaja\'s lake.This 100 year old house has been completely renovated and
        offers you all of the comforts. At the same time we have kept its old, homely, Latvian spirit.
        You will be enchanted by the decor of each of the rooms in Ezera Maja. Even the tiniest detail
        has been made with the special love of an artist’s hand. The rooms are equipped using natural
        local materials, keeping the ancient feel of the house.</string>
    
</resources>
