<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Liepaja Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="category_classics">Classics</string>
    <string name="category_active_leisure">Active Leisure</string>
    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_dining">Dining</string>

    <!-- Active Leisure -->
    <string name="tarzan">Tarzan\'s Obstacle Park</string>
    <string name="tarzan_description">Tarzan\'s Obstacle Park consists of 5 tracks and 76 different
        obstacles placed in trees up to 15 meters above the ground. It will be interesting for both
        children and adults, since the tracks are tailored to different interests.</string>
    <string name="karosta_prison">Karosta Prison</string>
    <string name="karosta_prison_description">Offers guided tours in Karosta Prison and museum, show
        "Behind Bars", accommodation and Extreme Night in prison. Different activities in Northern
         Forts like guided tour, Spy game Escape from USSR and Labyrinth of Senses.</string>
    <string name="children_playground">Children Playground</string>
    <string name="children_playground_description">Every Sunday from June 1st till September 1st at
        midday 12:00 leisure activities, puppet theatre or cirkus performances for children.</string>
    <string name="archery_range">"Archery Liepaja" 3D archery range</string>
    <string name="arechery_range_description">There are up to 20 different 3D animal targets in the
        3D archery range, which are placed so that anyone would be able to shoot.</string>
    <string name="windsurfing_club">Windsurfing Club "Rietumkrasts"</string>
    <string name="windsurfing_club_description">Recreation on the water - windsurfing, kite-surfing,
        water-skiing, bladders, water-motorbikes, motorboats. Rentals and lessons. Portable kitchen,
        sauna, tent places.</string>
    <string name="bb_wakepark">Active Leisure Park "BB wakepark"</string>
    <string name="bb_wakepark_description">In summer, "BB wakepark" has the variety of offers as
        wakeboarding track and equipment rentals, SUP board and boats rental, and for the full
        relaxation, sauna and hot-tub services.</string>
    <string name="boat_rental">Boat rental "Niknās laivas"</string>
    <string name="boat_rental_description">Furious and comfortable boat rental for trips in Liepāja
        Trade Canal and Lake, as well as in rivers of Kurzeme.</string>
    <string name="quest_house">Quest House</string>
    <string name="quest_house_description">Quest House – is a unique adventure – offers you an
        interesting team game for groups of 2-4 people. You get locked in a room, in  order to
        escape you should examine all hides, using hints and clues solve all riddles, applying your
        logics and savvy.</string>
    <string name="ship_and_catamaran_rent">Ship Četri vēji and catamaran rent</string>
    <string name="ship_and_catamaran_rent_description">Boat trips in Liepāja port area and the sea.
        Boarding at the yacht port in Liepāja promenade. Fishing in the sea and long boat trips.</string>


    <!-- Nature -->
    <string name="liepaja_lake">Liepaja Lake</string>
    <string name="liepaja_lake_description">A lagoon-type lake that was formed with the retreat of
        the Baltic Sea. An important waterfowl nesting and transit place during migration periods.
        During the nesting period many bird species that are threatened in Europe find their shelter
        here. The lake and its surrounding meadows are a nature reserve area. There are two bird
        watching towers one the lake.</string>
    <string name="liepaja_beach">Liepaja Beach</string>
    <string name="liepaja_beach_description">The beach is 50 to 80 m wide when the wind is calm, and
        it has white fine sand which amazes even those who have been to the world\'s most famous
        beach resorts. After a strong wind you can find some pieces of amber washed ashore. \n
        Liepāja has a first beach in Latvia, adjusted for people with special needs.</string>
    <string name="seaside_park">Seaside Park</string>
    <string name="seaside_park_description">Liepaja is very proud of the park. It was developed at
        the end of the 19th century. The park is 3 km long with a total area of 70 ha and is one of
        the largest planted parks in Latvia. It is the home of Latvias largest drums, nouveau
        fountain, The Swan Pond, Monument for sailors and fishermen lost at sea, children
        playground and much more.</string>
    <string name="raina_park">Raina Park</string>
    <string name="raina_park_description">This is a landscape park, developed at the 19th century.
        Also has a children playground</string>
    <string name="southern_breakwater">Sauthern Breakwater</string>
    <string name="southern_breakwater_description">When having a walk on the beach, supplement it
    with a sightseeing on the Sauthern Breakwater for even nicer memories.</string>
    <string name="northern_breakwater">Northern Breakwater</string>
    <string name="northern_breakwater_description">1800 meters long, this breakwater is a famous
        place for the locals to enjoy the beaty of nature during storms.</string>
    <string name="seaside_park_velo_track">Seaside Velo-track</string>
    <string name="seaside_park_velo_track_description">The Seaside Velo-track is a beautiful place
        in Liepaja for bike rides and strolls. You\'ll wish you could take the pine and sea smell
        with you!</string>
    <!-- Classics -->


    <!-- Dining -->


    <!-- Hotels -->

</resources>
